<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Introduction</string>
    <string name="content"><i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> received his BS degree in mechanical engineering in 1994 from National Sun-Yet-Sen University and his MS degree in mechanical engineering in 1998 from National Chiao Tung University, where he get his PhD degree in Computer Science in 2006 from National Chiao Tung University. His recent research interests include mobile device programming, image sharing, pattern recognition,, image processing and e-learning.\n
      \n<b>HomePage:</b> http://140.138.146.85\n\n
        <b>Journal papers</b>\n
⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> and Jiu-Sheng Kuo,\"Using Storyboard To Improve Video Retarget Quality by Pattern Matching Method\", International Journal of Computer Science Engineering and Information Technology Research (IJCSEITR), Vol.6, No.3, 2016, 8, pp. 1-8
Pei-Yu Lin, Ran-Zan Wang, Yu-Jie Chang, \n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Prevention of cheating in visual cryptography by using coherent patterns,”Information Science, Vol. 301, No. 20, 2015, 4, pp. 61-74 .(SCI) 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “A Data Hiding Method which the Secret Image Exist after Cropping Style Image Resigning,”Journal of Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(JIH-MSP), Vol. 6, No. 2, 2015, 1, pp. 365-370.(EI) 
\n⊙Chii-Jen Chen, You-Wei Wang, Wei-Chih Shen, Chih-Yi Chen, <i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “The Lobe Fissure Tracking by the Modified Ant Colony Optimization Framework in CT Images,”Algorithms, Vol. 7, No. 4, 2014, 12, pp. 635-649.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Chun­Hung Lai, “A Fast Image Resampling Method,”International Journal of Computer Science and Network Security, Vol. 14, No. 12, 2014, 12, pp. 16-19. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Android Saisiyat and Chinese Translation System with Speech Recognition,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 6, No. 1, 2014, 12, pp. 38-40. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Encrypt Text Style Data by Language Translation Approach,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 6, No. 1, 2014, 12, pp.57-58. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Zai-Xuan Liao,Zhen-Mu Li，\"The Study on Automatic Authentification for Android\" ,International Journal of Advanced Information Technologies(IJAIT)，Vol.8 , No.1，2014.6.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, \"A Study on Information Reservation for Visual Secret Sharing Method with Reversible Style,\"Journal of Communication and Computer, Vol. 10, 2013, 10, pp. pp.643-648. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Jia-Hao Hsu, Wei-chi Cheng, \"Text-Based Visual Secret Sharing,\"International Journal of Computer Science and Network Security, Vol. 13, No. 30, 2013, 5, pp. 38-40. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “A Curve Matching Algorithm for Constrainted System,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 4, No. 1, 2012, 12, pp. 1-4.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Minimum Spanning Tree for Variant Weighting,”International Journal of Computer Secience and Network Security, Vol. 12, No. 7, 2012, 7, pp. 68-70.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Lossless Data Hiding on 3-D Triangle Mesh,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 3, No. 1, 2011, 12, pp. 13-16.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Ming-Hway Huang, Shun-Yi Pen, “A Study of Watermarking Based on Cryptography,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 3, No. 1, 2011, 12, pp. 37-41.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Ren-Kai Wu, “An Interactive Rear-projector by Image Processing and Pattern Recognition Approach,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 3, No. 1, 2011, 12, pp. 1-5.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Lossless Data Hiding on 3-D Triangle Mesh,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 3, No. 1, 2011, 12, pp. 13-16.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Ming-Hway Huang, Shun-Yi Pen, “A Study of Watermarking Based on Cryptography,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 3, No. 1, 2011, 12, pp. 37-41.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Safe Secret Image Sharing with Fault Tolerance Key,”International Journal of Computer Science and Network Security, Vol. 10, No. 10, 2011, 9, pp. 20-23.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Secret Sharing for Object Structure Data,”International Journal of Computer Science and Network Security, Vol. 10, No. 11, 2010, 11,pp.6-9 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Tsung-Hsien Lai, “Image Base Ball Speed Estimation for Tennis Video,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 2, No. 1, 2010, 12, pp. 9-12.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “A Survey for Visual Sharing Scheme with Geometry Property,”Journal of Image Processing and Communication, Vol. 2, No. 1, 2010, 12, pp. 35-39.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Chiu-Jian Hsu, Mei-Ling Lin, “Maximizing the Secret Hiding Ratio in Visual Secret Sharing with Reversible Property,”International Journal of Computer and Network Security, Vol. 9, No. 7, 2009, 7, pp.1-6.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Non-expansion Visual Secret Sharing in Reversible Style,”International Journal of Computer and Network Security, Vol. 9, No. 2, 2009, 2, pp. 204-208
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Friendly Progressive Visual Secret Sharing,”Pattern Recognition, Vol. 41, No. 4, 2008, 4, pp. 1410-1414. (SCI,IP:2.019) 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Quality Controllable Progressive Secret Image Sharing – Discrete Cosine Transform Approach,”International Journal of Education and Information Technologys, No. 1, 2007, 10, pp. 43-47.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Ja-Chen Lin, “Universal Share for the Sharing of Multiple Images,” Journal of the Chinese Institute of Engineers , Vol. 30, No. 4, 2007, 6, pp. 753-757. (SCI,EI) 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> and Ja-Chen Lin, “Progressive Viewing and Sharing of Sensitive Images” Pattern Recognition and Image Analysis, no.4 Vol.16, 2006, 8, 638-642. (EI) 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “A Data Hiding Method for Multi-layer Protection Using Sensitive Transformation” WSEAS Transactions on Information Science and Application, 2006, 45-49. (EI) 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “A Multiple-Shots Method to Overcome Metering Problem for Ordinary Digital Cameras” International Journal on Graphics, Vision and Image Processing, 6, 2006, 7, 13-17. 
Chih-Ching Thein, \n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> and Ja-Chen Lin, “Sharing Secret Images by Using Base-transform and Small-size Host images” International Journal of Computer Science and Network Security, 6, 2006, 7, 219-225. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> and Ja-Chen Lin, “Multi-channel Secret Image Transmission with Fast Decoding: by using Bit-level Sharing and Economic-size Shares” International Journal of Computer and Network Security, 6, 2006, 6, 228-234. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> and Ja-Chen Lin, “Visual Cryptography with Extra Ability of Hiding Confidential Data” Journal of Electronic Imaging, 15, 2006, 4. 023020(SCI,IP:0.801)
Fang-Pang Lin, Wei-Fone Tsai and <i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> “Data Warehousing and Meshing for large Scale Dataset from Surveyed Profiles of Watercourses” Computaional Geometry , 10, 1998, 3, 239-247.
\n\n<b>Conference papers </b>\n⊙
International\n⊙
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Yu-Feng Huang and Yu-Chien Chang, \"An Emotion Recognition System for Home Care Application\", 2018 International Conference on Smart Science(ICSS2018), ), Kyoto, Japan ,2018,3,30－2018,4,2.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> and Pei-Ru Tsai, “A Study on Predicting the Timing of Drop by Low Coast Brainwave Device,”The 6th Annual Conference on Engineering and Information Technology(ACEAIT2018), Kyoto, Japan ,2018,3,27－2018,3,29.
\n⊙Chia-Chen Yeh,<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>,\"A study on immersive user experience for game activity with third person perspective device\", 2017 International Conference for Top and Emerging Computer Scientists (IC-TECS 2018),Dec 21-24, 2017 Taipei.
\n⊙Yu-Chien Chang,<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>,\"Using brainwave information to implement a novel color selection tool\", 2017 International Conference for Top and Emerging Computer Scientists (IC-TECS 2017),Dec 21-24, 2017 Taipei.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Chia-Chen Yeh, Yu-Chien Chang,\"A study on the influence of operating motion in real world with third person perspective\", 2017 International Conference for Top and Emerging Computer Scientists (IC-TECS 2017),Dec 21-24, 2017 Taipei.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>,Yu-Feng Huang, Lu-Hsuan Li andYan-Ru Pan,\"Using Color Converting to Hide Image Information\", IEEE Proceeding on The Thirteenth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2017), August 12-15, 2017 Matsue, Shimane, Japan(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>,Yan-Jiang,Jiu-Sheng Kuo and Verna Ip,\"Using Digital Hiding to Revitalize Traditional Chinese Proverb\", IEEE Proceeding on The Thirteenth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2017), August 12-15, 2017 Matsue, Shimane, Japan(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, An Meta Framework Designing For Auto Video Retargeting, 2016 International Conference for Top and Emerging Computer Scientists (IC-TECS 2016), 2016, Dec 22-25, Taipei.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, \"Unexpected Contours Removing Method for Projector,\" IEEE Proceeding on The Third International Symposium on Computer, Consumer and Control(IS3C2016), 2016, July 4-6, Xi\'an, China. (EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> and Jiu-Sheng Kuo, “Using Storyboard to Improve Video Retarget Quality by Pattern Matching Method,”The 4th Annual Conference on Engineering and Information Technology(ACEAIT2016), Kyoto, Japan ,2016,3,29－2016,3,31.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Chun Li, Yu-Jui Hu, Wen-Chi Peng, “A Data Hiding Method for Image Retargeting,”The Eighth International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing ICGEC-2014), Ganjiang Hotel, Nanchang, China, 2014, 10, 18－2014, 10, 20. 
\n⊙Shang-Kuan Chen, Cheng-Wei Huan, Ran-Zan Wang, Wen-Pin Fang, “Rendering 3D Soild Model,”The Eighth International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing (ICGEC-2014), Ganjiang Hotel, Nanchang, China, 2014, 10, 18－2014, 10, 20.
\n⊙Shang-Kuan Chen, Shang-Kuan Chen, Ran-Zan Wang, <i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “High-payload lossless data hiding scheme with block statistics characteristics,”IEEE Proceeding on The Tenth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2014), Kitakyushu, Kitakyushu, Janpan, 2014, 8, 27－2014, 8, 29.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Ran-Zan Wang, Shang-Kuan Chen, Yeuan-Kuen Lee, “Data Transmission System for Mobile Device by Audio Hiding approach,”IEEE Proceeding on The Tenth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2014), Kitakyushu, Kitakyushu, Japan, 2014, 8, 27－2014, 8, 29. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Ming-Hao Liu, Yeuan-Kuen Lee, Rei-Heng Cheng, “Video Resizing for Mobile Device,”IEEE Proceeding onThe Tenth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2014), Kitakyushu, Kitakyushu, Japan, 2014, 8, 27－2014, 8, 29. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Chun Li, Tsu-Hsun Fu, “Real-Time Broadcast System for Android System,”IEEE Proceeding on The Tenth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2014), Kitakyushu, Kitakyushu, Japan, 2014, 8, 27－2018, 8, 29. 
\n⊙Chii-Jen Chen, Chii-Jen Chen, You-Wei Wang, <i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “A Study on Captcha Recognition,”IEEE Proceeding on The Tenth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2014), Kitakyushu, Kitakyushu, Japan, 2014, 8, 27－2014, 8, 29.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Sheng-Hsuan Lu, Ming-Hao Liu, Ting-Hung Lai,, Shan-Chun Hung, Yin-Feng Huang, Chii-Jen Chen, “International Symposium on Computer, Consumer and Control 2014,”A Web Base Android Application Development System, Evergreen Laurel Hotel, TaiChung, Taiwan, 2014, 6, 10－2014, 6, 12. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Jia-Hao Hsu, Chun Li, Ran-Zan Wang, “A Study on Stoke Gestures Recognition for Resource Constraint Application,”Annual Conference on Engineering and Information Technology(ACEAIT 2014), Toshi Center Hotel, Touko, Japan, 2014, 3, 28－2014, 3, 30.
Ching-Min Hu, Ran-Zan Wang, Shang-Kuan Chen, \n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Yu-Jie Chang, Yeuan-Kuen Lee, \"A Novel Data Hiding Method Using Sphere Encoding,\"IEEE Proceeding on The Seventh International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing(ICGEC2013), the Faculty of Mathematics and Physics of the Char, Prague, Czech Republic, 2013, 8, 25－2013, 8, 27. 
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Ran-Zan Wang, Shang-Kuan Chen, \"Non-Expanding Friendly Visual Cryptography,\"IEEE Proceeding on The Seventh International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing(ICGEC2013), the Faculty of Mathematics and Physics of the Char, Prague, Czech Republic, 2013, 8, 25－2013, 8, 27.
\n⊙Shang-Kuan Chen, Gen-Han Wu, Yen-Wu Ti, Ran-Zan Wang, <i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Chian-Jhu Lu, \"Hierarchical particle swarm optimization algorithm of IPSVR problem,\"IEEE Proceeding on The Seventh International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing(ICGEC2013), the Faculty of Mathematics and Physics of the Char, Prague, Czech Republic, 2013, 8, 25－2013, 8, 27.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Chii-Jen Chen, “A Study on Information Reservation for Visual Secret Sharing Method with Reversible Style,”The 2nd International Conference on Engineering and Applied Science (2013 ICEAS), Toshi Center, Toyko, Japan, 2013, 3, 15－2013, 3, 17.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “An Intelligent Hand Gesture Extraction and Recognition System for Home Care Application,”the Sixth International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing (ICGEC-2012), 北九州国際会議場, Kitakyushu, Japan, 2012, 8, 24－2012, 8, 28.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Offline QR Code Authorization Based on Visual Cryptography ,”IEEE Proceeding on The Seventh International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP 2011), Dalian, Dalian, China, 2011, 10, 14－2011, 10, 16.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Fast Decoding method for On-Line Visual Secret Sharing by Parallel Processing Approach ,”IEEE Proceeding on Conference on The Seventh International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP 2011), Dalian, Dalian, China, 2011, 10, 14－2011, 10, 16.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Shun-Yi Pen, “A Mobile Phone Base Sensory Integration Training Software,”IEEE Proceeding on The Fifth International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing(ICGEC 2011) , Kinmen University, Kinmen, Taiwan, 2011, 8, 29－2010, 9, 1.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Reversible Visible Watermarking for Contour Style Logo,”IEEE Proceeding on The Fourth International Conference on Genetic and Evolutionary Computing(ICGEC 2010), Shenzhen Graduate School of Harbin Institute of Te, Shenzhen, China, 2010, 12, 13－2010, 12, 15.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Multi-layer Secret Image Sharing,”IEEE Proceeding on The Sixth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP 2010), Darmstadt, Darmstadt, Germany, 2010, 10, 15－2010, 10, 17.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Parallel Processing for Secret Image Sharing,”International Symposium on Parallel and Distributed IEEE Proceeding on Processing with Applications (ISPA10) , National Taiwan University of Science and Technolo, Taipei, Taiwan, 2010, 9, 6－2010, 9, 9.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Non-expansion Hiding Secret Image in Visual Secret Sharing with Shift Style ,”Proceeding on IEEE 2009 the Fifth International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing (IIHMSP-2009), Mielparque Kyoto, Kyoto, Japan, 2009, 9, 12－2009, 9, 14.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Content supply computer system,”Proceeding on IEEE 2009 International Conference on Future Computer and Communication (ICFCC 2009), Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 2009, 4, 3－2009, 4, 5.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Sen-Jen Lin, “Fast Secret Image Sharing Scheme in HPC,”Proceeding on the 10th International Conference on High-Performance Computing in Asia-Pacific Region(HPC ASIA 2009) joint WorkShop on PC-Grid, Grand Hi-Lai Hotel, Kaohsiung, Taiwan, 2009, 3, 2－2009, 3, 5.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Secret Image Sharing Safety,”Proceeding on IEEE International Conference on the 14th Asia-Pacific Conference on Communications (APCC2008), Akihabara, Tokyo, Japan, 2008, 10, 14－2008, 10, 16.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, Hong-Ru Lee, Fang-Pang Lin, “An novel two layer user identification Method,”Proceeding on IEEE International Conference on Intelligence and Security Informatics (ISI2008), Grand Formosa Regent Hotel, Taipei, Taiwan, 2008, 6, 17－2008, 6, 20.(EI)
\n⊙Sen-Jen Lin, Ja-Chen Lin, <i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>,“Visual cryptography (VC) with non-expanded shadow images: a hilbert-curve approach,”Proceeding on IEEE International Conference on Intelligence and Security Informatics (ISI2008), Grand Formosa Regent Hotel, Taipei, Taiwan, 2008, 6, 17－2008, 6, 20.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Visual Cryptography in reversible style,”IEEE Proceeding on the Third International Conference on Intelligent Information Hiding and Multimedia Signal Processing(IIHMSP2007), Kaohsiung, Taiwan, R.O.C, 2007, 11, 26～2007, 11, 28.(EI)
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i>, “Multi-layer Progressive Secret Image Sharing,”7th WSEAS Int. Conf. on Signal Processing, Computational Geometry and Artificial Vision, Vouliagmeni Beach, Athen, Greece, 2007, 8, 24～2007, 8, 26.
\n⊙<i>Wen-Pinn Fang</i> ,“Combining Copyright Protection and Data Hiding – A Sensitive Transformation Approach” 6th WSEAS Int. Conf. on Signal Processing, Computational Geometry and Artificial Vision,Agios Nikolaos, 2006,8 .</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="wen_pinn_fang">Wen-Pinn Fang</string>
</resources>
